pathologyoutlines.com 2019-12-31

# Pathology Outlines - Privacy Policy

**Page views in 2018:** 109

 **Page views in 2019 to date:** 176

Privacy Notice

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for PathologyOutlines.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following: 

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared. 
  2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data. 
  3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information. 
  4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

Information Collection, Use and Sharing  
This is a no registration website. We do not collect any information on this site, other than as indicated below. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.  
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to mail an invoice.  
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

Your Access to and Control Over Information  
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

  * See what data we have about you, if any. 
  * Change/correct any data we have about you. 
  * Have us delete any data we have about you. 
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data. 

Security  
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.  
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the Web page.  
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

Advertising  
We request information from you when you advertise with us, including contact information (name and address) and financial information (credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you.

Cookies  
We use "cookies" on this site for Google Analytics tracking. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

Links  
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

Surveys & Contests  
From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and mailing address), and demographic information (such as institution). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

**If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 248-646-0325 or via email to[NatPernick@gmail.com](mailto:NatPernick@gmail.com).**
